Guide to the Donohoe Kelly & Co. Records, 1863-1917 JL002
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series B. General Account Books
  - Daybook (Nat'l Shawmut Bank), Dec 1894-Aug 1906 (Volume 29)
  - Blotter, 1894-1898 (Volume 30)
  - Blotter, 1898-1901 (Volume 31)
  - Blotter, 1901-1904 (Volume 32)
  - Blotter, 1905-1906 (Volume 33)
  - Blotter, 1907-1909 (Volume 34)
  - Blotter, 1909-1911 (Volume 35)
  - Blotter, 1911-1913 (Volume 36)
  - Blotter, 1913-1915 (Volume 37)
  - Blotter, 1915-1917 (Volume 38)
  - Blotter, 1917-1919 (Volume 39)
  - Blotter, 1919-1921 (Volume 40)
  - Blotter, 1921-1923 (Volume 41)
  - Blotter, 1923-1925 (Volume 42)
  - General Ledger Blotters, 1872-1876 (Volume 43)
  - General Ledger Blotters, 1881-1887 (Volume 44)
  - General Ledger Blotters, 1887-1891 (Volume 45)
  - General Cash, 1866-1868 (Volume 46)
  - General Cash, 1869-1870 (Volume 47)
  - General Cash, 1871-1872 (Volume 48)
  - General Cash, 1873-1874 (Volume 49)
  - General Cash, 1875- (Volume 50)
  - General Cash, 1877-1878 (Volume 51)
  - General Cash, 1879-1880 (Volume 52)
  - General Cash, 1881-1882 (Volume 53)
  - General Cash (Volume 54)
  - General Cash, 1884-1885 (Volume 55)
  - General Cash, 1886-1887 (Volume 56)
  - General Cash, 1888-1889 (Volume 57)
  - General Cash, 1890-1893 (Volume 58)
  - General Cash, 1891-1893 (Volume 59)
  - General Cash, 1894- (Volume 60)
  - General Cash, 1897-1898 (Volume 61)
  - General Cash, 1897-1898 (Volume 62)
  - General Cash, 1899-1900 (Volume 63)
  - General Cash, 1901-1902 (Volume 64)
  - General Cash, 1903-1904 (Volume 65)
  - General Cash, 1905 (Volume 66)
  - General Cash, 1906 (Volume 67)
  - General Cash, 1907 (Volume 68)
  - General Cash, 1908 (Volume 69)
  - General Cash, 1909 (Volume 70)
  - General, 1910 (Volume 71)
  - General Cash, 1911 (Volume 72)
  - General Cash, 1912 (Volume 73)
  - General Cash, 1913 (Volume 74)
  - General Cash, 1914 (Volume 75)
  - General Cash, 1915 (Volume 76)
  - General Cash, 1916 (Volume 77)
  - General Cash, 1917 (Volume 78)
  - General Cash, 1918 (Volume 79)
  - General Cash, 1919 (Volume 80)
  - General Cash, 1920 (Volume 81)
  - General Cash, 1921 (Volume 82)
  - General Cash, 1922 (Volume 83)
  - General Cash, 1923 (Volume 84)
  - General Cash, 1924 (Volume 85)
  - General Cash Items, May 1906-Sept 1907 (Volume 86)
  - General Cash Items, Sept 1907-Oct 1908 (Volume 87)
  - Credit Cash (A-J), 1864-1866 (Volume 88)
  - Credit Cash (K-Z), 1864-1866 (Volume 89)
  - Credit Cash (A-J), 1866-1868 (Volume 90)
  - Credit Cash (K-Z), 1866-1868 (Volume 91)
  - Credit Cash (A-J), 1868-1869 (Volume 92)
  - Credit Cash (K-Z), 1868-1869 (Volume 93)
  - Credit Cash (A-J), 1870-1871 (Volume 94)
  - Credit Cash (K-Z), 1870-1871 (Volume 95)
  - Credit Cash (A-J), 1871-1872 (Volume 96)
  - Credit Cash (A-J), 1872-1873 (Volume 97)
  - Credit Cash (K-Z), 1872-1873 (Volume 98)
  - Addenda: Cash book, 1877-1881
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, April-Dec 1901 (Volume 99)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, Jan-Aug 1902 (Volume 100)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, Aug 1902-April 1903 (Volume 101)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, April-Dec 1903 (Volume 102)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, Dec 1903-July 1904 (Volume 103)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, Aug 1904-March 1905 (Volume 104)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, March 1905-Nov 1905 (Volume 105)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, Nov 1905-Aug 1906 (Volume 106)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, Aug 1906-April 1907 (Volume 107)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, April-Dec 1907 (Volume 108)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, Dec 1907-July 1908 (Volume 109)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, July 1908-Feb 1909 (Volume 110)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, Feb-Sept 1909 (Volume 111)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, Sept 1909-April 1910 (Volume 112)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, April-Nov 1910 (Volume 113)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, Nov 1910-June 1911 (Volume 114)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, June 1911-Jan 1912 (Volume 115)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, Jan-Aug 1912 (Volume 116)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, Oct 1906-March 1908 (Volume 117)
    General note
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, March 1908-March 1910 (Volume 118)
  - Receiving Teller's Cash, March 1910-Feb 1912 (Volume 119)
  - Paying Teller's Cash, May-Nov 1906 (Volume 120)
  - Paying Teller's Cash, July-Dec 1909 (Volume 121)
  - Paying Teller's Cash, Jan-June 1910 (Volume 122)
  - Paying Teller's Cash, June-Dec 1910 (Volume 123)
  - Paying Teller's Cash, Jan-June 1911 (Volume 124)
  - Paying Teller's Cash, June-Dec 1911 (Volume 125)
  - Paying Teller's Daily Report, Dec 1886-April 1888 (Volume 126)
  - Paying Teller's Daily Report, April 1888-July 1889 (Volume 126a)
  - Paying Teller's Daily Report, July 1889-Nov 1890 (Volume 127)
  - Paying Teller's Daily Report, Nov 1890-Feb 1892 (Volume 127a)
  - Paying Teller's Daily Report, June 1893-Sept 1894 (Volume 128)
  - Paying Teller's Daily Report, Oct 1894-Jan 1896 (Volume 128a)
  - Paying Teller's Daily Report, Jan 1896-May 1897 (Volume 129)
  - Paying Teller's Daily Report, Sept 1898-Dec 1899 (Volume 130)
  - Paying Teller's Daily Report, Dec 1899-April 1901 (Volume 130a)
  - Paying Teller's Daily Report, April 1901-Dec 1902 (Volume 131)
  - Paying Teller's Daily Report, Dec 1902-July 1904 (Volume 132)
  - Paying Teller's Daily Report, July 1904-March 1906 (Volume 133)
  - Paying Teller's Daily Report, March 1906-Dec 1907 (Volume 134)
  - Paying Teller's Daily Report, Dec 1907-July 1909 (Volume 135)
  - Exchange Teller's Cash, Jan 1893-Aug 1895 (Volume 136)
  - Exchange Teller's Cash, Aug 1895-March 1898 (Volume 137)
  - Exchange Teller's Cash, March 1898-Sept 1900 (Volume 138)
  - Teller's Cash, 1904-1906 (Volume 139)
  - Teller's Cash, March-Nov 1909 (Volume 140)
  - Teller's Cash, Nov 1909-June 1910 (Volume 141)
  - Teller's Cash, March-Oct 1911 (Volume 142)
  - Teller's Daily Report, July 1909-Feb 1911 (Volume 143)
  - Teller's Daily Report, Feb 1911-Oct 1912 (Volume 144)
  - Checks and Deposits (A-E), 1891 (Volume 145)
    NOTE: Volumes of Checks and Deposits belong to 3 series of dates.
    Series 1: 145-215
    Series 2: 216-270
    Series 3: 271-280
    The last three volumes of Checks and Deposits apparently belong to no series.
  - (F-M), 1891 (Volume 146)
  - (N-Z), 1891 (Volume 147)
  - (A-E), 1892 (Volume 148)
  - (F-Mc), 1892 (Volume 149)
  - (N-Z), 1892 (Volume 150)
  - (A-E), 1894 (Volume 151)
  - (F-Mc), 1894 (Volume 152)
  - (N-Z), 1894 (Volume 153)
  - (A-E), 1895 (Volume 154)
  - (F-Mc), 1895 (Volume 155)
  - (N-Z), 1895 (Volume 156)
  - (A-E), 1897 (Volume 157)
  - (F-M), 1897 (Volume 158)
  - (N-Z), 1897 (Volume 159)
  - (A-E), 1898 (Volume 160)
  - (F-M), 1898 (Volume 161)
  - (N-Z), 1898 (Volume 162)
  - (A-E), 1899 (Volume 163)
  - (F-M), 1899 (Volume 164)
  - (N-Z), 1899 (Volume 165)
  - (A-E), 1900 (Volume 166)
  - (F-M), 1900 (Volume 167)
  - (N-Z), 1900 (Volume 168)
  - (A-E), 1902 (Volume 169)
  - (F-M), 1902 (Volume 170)
  - (N-Z), 1902 (Volume 171)
  - (A-E), 1903 (Volume 172)
  - (F-M), 1903 (Volume 173)
  - (N-Z), 1903 (Volume 174)
  - (A-E), 1904 (Volume 175)
  - (F-M), 1904 (Volume 175a)
  - (N-Z), 1904 (Volume 176)
  - (A-E), 1904 (Volume 177)
  - (F-M), 1904 (Volume 178)
  - (N-Z), 1904 (Volume 179)
  - (A-E), 1905 (Volume 180)
  - (F-M), 1905 (Volume 181)
  - (N-Z), 1905 (Volume 182)
  - (A-E), 1906 (Volume 183)
  - (F-M), 1906 (Volume 184)
  - (N-Z), 1906 (Volume 185)
  - (A-E), 1908 (Volume 186)
  - (F-M), 1908 (Volume 187)
  - (N-Z), 1907-1908 (Volume 188)
  - (A-E), 1909 (Volume 189)
  - (F-M), 1909 (Volume 190)
  - (N-Z), 1909 (Volume 191)
  - Checks and Deposits (A-E), 1910 (Volume 192)
  - (F-Mc), 1910 (Volume 193)
  - (N-Z), 1910 (Volume 194)
  - (A-E), 1911 (Volume 195)
  - (F-Mc), 1911 (Volume 196)
  - (N-Z), 1911 (Volume 197)
  - (A-E), 1912 (Volume 198)
  - (F-Mc), 1912 (Volume 199)
  - (N-Z), 1912 (Volume 200)
  - (A-E), 1913 (Volume 201)
  - (F-Mc), 1913 (Volume 202)
  - (N-Z), 1913 (Volume 203)
  - (A-E), 1914 (Volume 204)
  - (F-Mc), 1914 (Volume 205)
  - (N-Z), 1914 (Volume 206)
  - (A-G, A-F), 1915 (Volume 207)
  - (H-O, G-N), 1915 (Volume 208)
  - (P-Z), 1915 (Volume 209)
  - (A-F), 1916 (Volume 210)
  - (G-N), 1916 (Volume 211)
  - (O-Z), 1916 (Volume 212)
  - (A-F), 1917 (Volume 213)
  - (G-N), 1917 (Volume 214)
  - (O-Z), 1917 (Volume 215)
  - (E-M), 1876 (Volume 216)
  - (F-Mc), 1876 (Volume 217)
  - (A-E), 1877 (Volume 218)
  - (F-Mc), 1877 (Volume 219)
  - (F-Mc), 1877 (Volume 220)
  - (N-Z), 1877-1878 (Volume 221)
  - (A-E), 1878 (Volume 222)
  - (F-Mc), 1878 (Volume 223)
  - (N-Z), 1878 (Volume 224)
  - (A-E), 1878-1879 (Volume 225)
  - (F-Mc), 1878-1879 (Volume 226)
  - (N-Z), 1878-1879 (Volume 227)
  - (A-E), 1878-1879 (Volume 228)
  - (F-Mc), 1878-1879 (Volume 229)
  - (N-Z), 1879-1880 (Volume 230)
  - (A-E), 1880 (Volume 231)
  - (F-Mc), 1880 (Volume 232)
  - (N-Z), 1880 (Volume 233)
  - (A-E), 1880 (Volume 234)
  - (F-Mc), 1879-1881 (Volume 235)
  - (N-Z), 1879-1881 (Volume 236)
  - (A-E), 1881 (Volume 237)
  - (F-Mc), 1881 (Volume 238)
  - (N-Z), 1881 (Volume 239)
  - (F-Mc), 1881 (Volume 240)
  - (F-Mc), 1881-1882 (Volume 241)
  - (A-J), 1882-1883 (Volume 242)
  - (K-Z), 1882 (Volume 243)
  - Checks and Deposits (A-J), 1884-1885 (Volume 244)
  - (K-Z), 1882-1883 (Volume 245)
  - (A-J), 1883 (Volume 246)
  - (K-Z), 1883 (Volume 247)
  - (A-J), 1883-1884 (Volume 248)
  - (K-Z), 1883-1884 (Volume 249)
  - (A-J), 1884 (Volume 250)
  - (K-Z), 1884 (Volume 251)
  - (A-J), 1883-1885 (Volume 252)
  - (K-Z), 1884 (Volume 253)
  - (K-Z), 1884-1885 (Volume 254)
  - (K-Z), 1885 (Volume 255)
  - (A-J), 1885-1886 (Volume 256)
  - (K-Z), 1885-1886 (Volume 257)
  - (A-J), 1886-1887 (Volume 258)
  - (K-Z), 1886-1887 (Volume 259)
  - (K-Z), 1887-1888 (Volume 260)
  - (A-J), 1888 (Volume 261)
  - (K-Z), 1888 (Volume 262)
  - (A-J), 1888-1889 (Volume 263)
  - (K-Z), 1888-1889 (Volume 264)
  - (A-J), 1889-1890 (Volume 265)
  - (K-Z), 1889-1890 (Volume 267)
  - (A-J), 1890 (Volume 268)
  - (K-Z), 1890 (Volume 269)
  - (A-J), 1890 (Volume 270)
  - (K-Z), 1875 (Volume 271)
  - (A-J), 1874 (Volume 272)
  - (K-Z), 1874 (Volume 273)
  - (A-J), 1875 (Volume 274)
  - (A-J), 1875-1876 (Volume 275)
  - (K-Z), 1875-1876 (Volume 276)
  - (A-E), 1876 (Volume 277)
  - (N-Z), 1876 (Volume 278)
  - (A-E), 1876-1877 (Volume 279)
  - (N-Z), 1876-1877 (Volume 280)
  - (A-J), 1882 (Volume 281)
  - (A-J), 1883 (Volume 282)
  - (A-J), 1886 (Volume 283)
  - Deposit Book (A-J), 1867-1869 (Volume 284)
  - Deposit Book (K-Z), 1867-1869 (Volume 285)
  - Deposit Book (A-J), 1870-1872 (Volume 286)
  - Deposit Book (K-Z), 1870-1872 (Volume 287)
  - Deposit Book (K-Z), 1872 (Volume 288)
  - Deposit Book (A-J), 1873 (Volume 289)
  - Daily Cash Accounts, July 1905-Dec 1906 (Volume 290)
  - Daily Cash Accounts, June 1906-Nov 1906 (Volume 291)
  - Daily Cash Accounts, May-Nov 1906 (Volume 292)
  - Daily Cash Accounts, Dec 1906-May 1907 (Volume 293)
  - Daily Cash Accounts, May-Nov 1907 (Volume 294)
  - Daily Cash Accounts, Nov 1906-June 1907 (Volume 295)
  - Daily Cash Accounts, June 1907-Jan 1908 (Volume 296)
  - Daily Cash Accounts, Jan -July 1908 (Volume 297)
  - Daily Cash Accounts, Feb 1908-Feb 1909 (Volume 298)
  - Daily Cash Accounts, March-Oct 1909 (Volume 299)
  - Daily Cash Accounts, Oct 1909-June 1910 (Volume 300)
  - Daily Cash Accounts, Feb-Sept 1911 (Volume 301)
  - Daily Cash Accounts, Jan-Aug 1913 (Volume 302)
  - Certificates of Deposit Register, 1883-1894 (Volume 303)
  - Certificates of Deposit (1-1000), April-Oct 1891 (Volume 304)
  - Certificates of Deposit (1001-2000), Oct 1891-June 1892 (Volume 305)
  - Certificates of Deposit (2001-3000), June 1892-Feb 1893 (Volume 306)
  - Certificates of Deposit (3001-4000), Feb 1893-Oct 1893 (Volume 307)
  - Certificates of Deposit (4001-5000), Oct 1893-April 1894 (Volume 308)
  - Certificates of Deposit (5001-6000), April-Nov 1894 (Volume 309)
  - “Mint” Journal, 1864-1925 (Volume 310)
  - Notes and Bills Receivable, 1880-1889 (Volume 311)
  - Bills Receivable, 1889-1905 (Volume 312)
  - Bills Receivable, 1898-1912 (Volume 313)
  - Bills Receivable, 1884-1895 (Volume 314)
  - Bills Receivable, 1906-1915 (Volume 315)
  - Interior Collections, 1890-Nov 1891 (Volume 316)
  - Interior Collections, Nov 1891-April 1893 (Volume 317)
  - Interior Collections, April 1893-May 1894 (Volume 318)
  - Interior Collections, June 1894-May 1897 (Volume 319)
  - Interior Collections, May 1897-Aug 1901 (Volume 320)
  - Interior Collections, Aug 1901-April 1905 (Volume 321)
  - Interior Collections, April 1905-May 1906 (Volume 322)
  - Interior Collections, Oct 1906-Oct 1914 (Volume 323)
  - Interior Collections, Dec 1903-Oct 1904 (Volume 324)
  - Interior Collections, Oct 1904-Sept 1905 (Volume 325)
  - Interior Collections, Sept 1905-Sept 1906 (Volume 326)
  - Interior Letters, June 1903-Feb 1904 (Volume 326a)
  - Interior Letters, June 1905-Jan 1906 (Volume 326b)
  - Country Collections, June 1894-Sept 1895 (Volume 327)
  - Country Collections, Sept 1895-Sept 1906 (Volume 328)
  - Country Collections, Sept 1896-July 1897 (Volume 329)
  - Country Collections, July 1897-Dec 1897 (Volume 330)
  - Country Collections, Jan 1898-Oct 1898 (Volume 331)
  - Country Collections, Oct 1898-May 1899 (Volume 332)
  - Country Collections, May 1899-Nov 1899 (Volume 333)
  - Country Collections, Feb-April 1906 (Volume 334)
  - Foreign and Eastern Collections, 1882-Oct 1889 (Volume 335)
  - Foreign and Eastern Collections, 1889-1894 (Volume 336)
  - Foreign and Eastern Collections, 1894-1898 (Volume 337)
  - Foreign and Eastern Collections, 1898-1901 (Volume 338)
  - Foreign and Eastern Collections, 1901-1904 (Volume 339)
  - Foreign and Eastern Collections, 1904-1906 (Volume 340)
  - Foreign and Eastern Collections, 1906-1907 (Volume 341)
  - Foreign and Eastern Collections, 1907-1909 (Volume 342)
  - Foreign and Eastern Collections, 1909-1910 (Volume 343)
  - Foreign and Eastern Collections, 1910 (Volume 344)
  - Foreign and Eastern Collections, 1910-1911 (Volume 345)
  - Foreign and Eastern Collections, 1911-1912 (Volume 346)
  - Foreign and Eastern Collections, 1912-1914 (Volume 347)
  - Eastern and Foreign Collections, May 1906 (Volume 347a)
  - Eastern Remittances, May 1906 (Volume 347b)
  - Collection Notes, 1864-1875 (Volume 348)
  - Collection Notes, 1876-1885 (Volume 349)
  - Collections (Alphabetical listings) (Volume 350)
  - Collections, 1889-1890 (Volume 351)
  - Collection letter book, Jan-Feb 1903 (Volume 352)
  - Nov 19-Dec 3, 1903 (Volume 353)
  - Dec 3-16, 1903 (Volume 354)
  - Dec 16-30, 1903 (Volume 355)
  - 1904 (Volume 356)
  - May-Sept 1906 (Volume 357)
  - Sept-Dec 1906 (Volume 358)
  - Jan 2-12, 1907 (Volume 359)
  - Jan 12-Feb 8, 1907 (Volume 360)
  - Feb 8-March 9, 1907 (Volume 361)
  - March 9-April 4, 1907 (Volume 362)
  - April 4-April 30, 1907 (Volume 363)
  - May 1907 (Volume 364)
  - June 1907 (Volume 365)
  - July 1907 (Volume 366)
  - August 1907 (Volume 367)
  - Sept 1907 (Volume 368)
  - Oct 1907 (Volume 368)
  - Nov-Dec 11, 1907 (Volume 370)
  - Dec 12-31, 1907 (Volume 371)
  - Addenda: 371a-, Jan 1908
  - Feb 1908 (Volume 372)
  - March 1908 (Volume 373)
  - April 1908 (Volume 374)
  - May 1908 (Volume 375)
  - June 1908 (Volume 376)
  - July 1908 (Volume 377)
  - August 1908 (Volume 378)
  - Sept 1908 (Volume 379)
  - Oct 1908 (Volume 380)
  - Nov 1908 (Volume 381)
  - Dec 1908 (Volume 382)
  - Jan 1909 (Volume 383)
  - Feb 1909 (Volume 384)
  - March 1909 (Volume 385)
  - April 1909 (Volume 386)
  - May 1909 (Volume 387)
  - June 1909 (Volume 388)
  - Addenda: 388a -, July 1909
  - August 1909 (Volume 389)
  - Sept 1909 (Volume 390)
  - Oct 1909 (Volume 391)
  - Nov 1909 (Volume 392)
  - Dec 1909 (Volume 393)
  - August 1912 (Volume 394)
  - Statements (Hibernian Banking Assoc.), Oct 1910-Feb 1911 (Volume 395)
  - Statements (Hibernian Banking Assoc.), Feb 1911-July 1911 (Volume 396)
  - Statements (Hibernian Banking Assoc.), July-Nov 191 (Volume 397)
  - Statements (Hibernian Banking Assoc.), Dec 1911-April 1912 (Volume 398)
  - Statements (Hibernian Banking Assoc.), April-Sept 1912 (Volume 399)
  - Statements (Hibernian Banking Assoc.), Sept 1912-Feb 1913 (Volume 400)
  - Statements (Hibernian Banking Assoc.), Feb-June 191 (Volume 401)
  - Statements (Bank of New York), April 1905-April 19 (Volume 401a)
  - Statements (Bank of New York), July-Nov 1906 (Volume 402)
  - Statements (Bank of New York), Nov 1906-March 1907 (Volume 403)
  - Statements (Bank of New York), March-July 1907 (Volume 404)
  - Statements (Bank of New York), July-Dec 1907 (Volume 405)
  - Statements (Bank of New York), Dec 1907-April 1908 (Volume 406)
  - Statements (Bank of New York), April-Sept 1908 (Volume 407)
  - Statements (Bank of New York), Sept 1908-Jan 1909 (Volume 408)
  - Statements (Bank of New York), Jan-May 1909 (Volume 409)
  - Statements (Bank of New York), June-Sept 1909 (Volume 410)
  - Statements (Bank of New York), Sept 1909-Feb 1910 (Volume 411)
  - Statements (Bank of New York), Feb-August 1910 (Volume 412)
  - Statements (Bank of New York), Aug 1910-Jan 1911 (Volume 413)
  - Statements (Bank of New York), Jan-July 1911 (Volume 414)
  - Statements (Bank of New York), July-Dec 1911 (Volume 415)
  - Statements (Bank of New York), Jan-June 1912 (Volume 416)
  - Statements (Bank of New York), June-Dec 1912 (Volume 417)
  - Statements (Bank of New York), Dec 1912-June 1913 (Volume 418)
  - Statements (Bank of the Manhattan Co.), Nov 1903-June 1905 (Volume 419)
  - Statements (Bank of the Manhattan Co.), July 1906-April 1907 (Volume 420)
  - Statements (Bank of the Manhattan Co.), April 1907-May 1908 (Volume 421)
  - Statements (Bank of the Manhattan Co.), June 1908-April 1909 (Volume 422)
  - Statements (Bank of the Manhattan Co.), April-Nov 1909 (Volume 423)
  - Statements (Bank of the Manhattan Co.), Nov 1909-April 1910 (Volume 424)
  - Statements (Bank of the Manhattan Co.), April 1910-Dec 1910 (Volume 425)
  - Statements (Bank of the Manhattan Co.), Dec 1910-June 1911 (Volume 426)
  - Statements (Bank of the Manhattan Co.), June 1911-Jan 1912 (Volume 427)
  - Statements (Bank of the Manhattan Co.), Jan-July 191 (Volume 428)
  - Statements (Bank of the Manhattan Co.), July-Dec 191 (Volume 429)
  - Statements (Bank of the Manhattan Co.), Dec 1912-June 1913 (Volume 430)
  - Statements (Mechanics-American Nat'l Bank) (Volume 431)
  - Statements (Mechanics-American Nat'l Bank), Oct 1910-Jan 1911
  - Statements (Mechanics-American Nat'l Bank), Feb-May 1911 (Volume 432)
  - Statements (Mechanics-American Nat'l Bank), May-Sept 1911 (Volume 433)
  - Statements (Mechanics-American Nat'l Bank), Sept 1911-Jan 1912 (Volume 434)
  - Statements (Mechanics-American Nat'l Bank), Jan-May 1912 (Volume 435)
  - Statements (Mechanics-American Nat'l Bank), May-Sept 1912 (Volume 436)
  - Statements (Mechanics-American Nat'l Bank), Sept 1912-Jan 1913 (Volume 437)
  - Statements (Mechanics-American Nat'l Bank), Jan-May 1913 (Volume 438)
  - Remittances for Collection, 1873-1876 (Volume 439)
  - Remittances for Collection, 1876-1878 (Volume 440)
  - Remittances for Collection, 1879-1880 (Volume 441)
  - Remittances for Collection, 1881-1883 (Volume 442)
  - Remittances for Collection, 1885-1886 (Volume 443)
  - Remittances for Collection, 1894-1896 (Volume 444)
  - Remittances to Hibernian Bking. Assoc., 1899-1901 (Volume 445)
  - Remittances to Hibernian Bking. Assoc., 1901-1904 (Volume 446)
  - Remittances to Hibernian Bking. Assoc., 1904-1906 (Volume 447)
  - Remittances to Bank of New York, June 1896-Sept 1897 (Volume 448)
  - Remittances to Bank of New York, Sept 1897-Oct 1898 (Volume 449)
  - Remittances to Bank of New York, Oct 1898-Sept 1899 (Volume 450)
  - Remittances to Bank of New York, Oct 1899-July 1900 (Volume 451)
  - Remittances to Bank of New York, July 1900-April 1901 (Volume 452)
  - Remittances to Bank of New York, Apr 1901-Dec 1901 (Volume 453)
  - Remittances to Bank of New York, July 1902-Feb 1903 (Volume 454)
  - Remittances to Bank of New York, Mar 1903-Aug 1906 (Volume 455)
  - Remittances to Bank of the Manhattan Co., 1901-1903 (Volume 456)
  - Remittances to Parr's Bank Ltd., London, 1906 (Volume 457)
  - Remittances to Consolidated Bank Ltd., London, 1891-1905 (Volume 458)
  - Remittances to American Exchange Bank, St. Louis, 1902-1904 (Volume 459)
  - Remittances to American Exchange, 1904-1906 (Volume 460)
  - Remittances to Andrï¿½, Neuflize and Cie, Paris, 1891-1906 (Volume 461)
  - Remittances to Third Nat'l Bank, Boston, 1896-1904 (Volume 462)
  - Advice of Drafts, August 1902-Oct 1903 (Volume 463)
  - Advices, Oct 1903-Oct 1904 (Volume 464)
  - Advices, Oct 1904-Oct 1905 (Volume 465)
  - Advices, Oct 1905-Feb 1907 (Volume 466)
  - Drafts: Hibernian Bking. Assoc., Jan 1883-May 1883 (Volume 467)
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, July 1904-Aug 1905
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, July 1905-Sept 1905
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Sept-Oct 1905
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Oct-Nov 1905
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Nov-Dec 1905 (Volume 468)
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Dec 1905-Feb 1906
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Feb-March 1906
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, March-July 1906
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, July-Sept 1906
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Sept-Oct 1906 (Volume 468)
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Oct-Dec 1906
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Dec 1906-Feb 1907
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Feb-April 1907
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, April-June 1907 (Volume 469)
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, June-July 1907
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, July-Sept 1907
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Sept-Nov 1907
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Nov-Dec 1907
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Dec 1907-Feb 1908
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Feb-April 1908
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, April-June 1908
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, June-August 1908
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, August-Sept 1908
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Sept-Nov 1908
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Nov 1908-Jan 1909
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Jan-March 1909 (Volume 470)
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, March-May 1909
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, May-June 1909
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, June-August 1909
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, August-Oct 1909
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Oct-Nov 1909
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Nov 1909-Jan 1910
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Jan-April 1910
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, April-June 1910
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, June-Sept 1910
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Sept-Dec 1910
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Dec 1910-Jan 1911
  - Drafts: Bank of New York, Feb-April 1911 (Volume 471)
  - Drafts on Chicago, July 1908-June 1909
  - Drafts on Boston, May 1905-March 1906
  - Drafts on Boston, March 1906-April 1907
  - Drafts: Bank of the Manhattan Co., July 1907-Jan 1908
  - Drafts: Bank of the Manhattan Co., Jan-June 1908
  - Drafts: Bank of the Manhattan Co., June-Oct 1908
  - Drafts: Bank of the Manhattan Co., Oct 1908-Jan 19
  - Drafts: Bank of the Manhattan Co., Jan-Apr 1909
  - Drafts: Bank of the Manhattan Co., April-July 1909
  - Drafts: Bank of the Manhattan Co., July-Oct 1909
  - Drafts: Bank of the Manhattan Co., Oct 1909-Jan 19 (Volume 472)
  - Drafts: Bank of the Manhattan Co., Jan-Mar 1910
  - Drafts: Bank of the Manhattan Co., Mar-May 1910
  - Drafts: Bank of the Manhattan Co., June-July 1910
  - Drafts: Bank of the Manhattan Co., July-Oct 1910
  - Drafts: Bank of the Manhattan Co., Oct-Nov 1910
  - Drafts: Bank of the Manhattan Co., Nov 1910-Feb 19
  - Drafts: Bank of the Manhattan Co., Mar-May 1911
  - Drafts: Bank of the Manhattan Co., May-July 1911
  - New York Drafts, April 1905-March 1906
  - New York Drafts, April-Oct 1906 (Volume 473)
  - Drafts, Oct 1906-Dec 1907 (Volume 473)
  - Drafts, Dec 1907-Sept 1909
  - Drafts, Dec 1907-August 1911
  - Drafts, Oct 1906-March 1907
  - Drafts, Oct 1906-August 1907
  - Drafts, March-July 1907
  - Drafts, August 1907-June 1908
  - Drafts, April 1907-May 1908